Love You to Death is a drama, tv movie film directed by Alex Kalymnios.
Inspired by a true story, this film tells the shocking tale of a mother and daughter who are
nothing like they seem, their tumultuous relationship ending in a brutal murder.
Camile Stoller, played by Marcia Gay Harden.
Esme Stoller, played by Emily Skeggs.
Travis Stoller, played by Tate Donovan.
Scott, played by Brennan Keel Cook.
Denise, played by Kayla Deorksen.
Alan, played by Kurt Ostlund.
Love You to Death is a 2019 crime drama film that aired on Lifetime.
The film is inspired by the murder of Dee Dee Blanchard and stars Marcia Gay Harden, Emily Skeggs,
Brennan Keel Cook, Garfield Wilson, Kayla Deorksen, Heather Doerksen, and Tate Donovan.
On January 27, 2019, a "special edition" of the film was aired that
featured behind-the-scene interviews with Harden and Skeggs.
The tone is dark and emotional.